22find.com 2008-10-04

# Privacy Policy

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**  
Thank you for visiting! We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, how we disclose it to third parties, and the choices you have regarding our use of and your ability to correct that information. 

**_What Information We Collect and How We Use It_**  
Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information and Aggregate Information. 

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. You may however, voluntarily provide the following Personally Identifiable Information: 

Contact information, such as name, email address, and physical address. 

We will maintain a record of your Personally Identifiable Information that will be sold or transferred to third parties that we believe offer products, services, and/or opportunities that are consistent with your expressed interests. Note that if you voluntarily provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, you consent to our sale, transfer, and use of your information. 

**_Aggregate Information:_** Aggregate Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") or the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.

**_Marketing_**  
We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to direct to you information, offers, products, and/or services from us and/or a third party. Your Personally Identifiable Information may, therefore, ultimately be used for marketing purposes by us and/or any one or more the third parties with which we work.

**_Sharing Your Information_**  
As disclosed above, we may sell or transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties. We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information with other related entities and/or business partners that provide services to us. 

**This Private Policy only applies to the Personally Identifiable Information that you disclose on the website. The Privacy Policy does not apply to third parties, such as companies to whom we sell, transfer, and/or share your Personally Identifiable Information. Since we are unable to control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies. We are not responsible for any information you provide to third parties.**

**Some third parties may be licensed to use our trademarks or service marks. The use of our trademarks or service marks is for reference or display purposes only.** Note that if you voluntarily provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, you understand and agree that we are not responsible or liable for any information you choose to provide to third parties in the future.  
From time to time, we may release or share with our corporate family Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use, to investigate unlawful activities, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. We may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to a court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

This site or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a merger or acquisition occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies serving you and other users of our Site. 

**_Security_**  
Your Personally Identifiable Information is temporarily stored on our servers in the United States. We treat your Personally Identifiable Information very carefully and use our best efforts to protect your Personally Identifiable Information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your Personally Identifiable Information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, we cannot promise, and you should not expect that your Personally Identifiable Information or private communications will always remain private. Moreover, this Privacy Policy only addresses the information that we collect from you. **This Private Policy does not apply to the Personally Identifiable Information that you disclose to others, such as bidders, buyers, or sellers on the Site or any other sites throughout the Internet. Since we are unable to control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties to whom you elect to disclose your information.**

**_Your Choices_**  
Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses. 

**_Accessing and Correcting Your Information_**  
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate and reliable for its intended use. However, after your information is sold to third parties, we can no longer access or review or correct your information. 

**_Protecting Your Information_**  
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, before the information is sold to third parties.

**_Use of Information Obtained from Site_**  
We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your Personally Identifiable Information once we sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties. We strongly encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of all these third parties to determine how they may use your Personally Identifiable Information.

**_Use of Cookies On This Site_**  
A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely.

Our Site may send cookies to your computer’s hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site. We do not use "surveillance" cookies that track your web activity outside of our Site.

**_Links To Other Web Sites_**  
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

**_Children's Privacy Protection_**  
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. We abide by the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and other relevant laws. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through an adult-oriented site, we will eliminate that data.

**_Changes To This Statement_**  
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.

**_Other Use of Your Information_**  
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other Personally Identifiable Information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

**_Contact Us_**  
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you with to access or make changes to information we have about you, please contact us at: LG Technology Attn: Privacy, 32840 Wolf Store Road, Temecula, CA 92592.

By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at that time of use.

Effective Date: December 26, 2007
